Finding aid for the Albert Kahn Associates records, 1825-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Architectural Drawings
  - Job No. 300-376
    - Cook Farm Company, Ltd., Office Building (Owen Building), Job No. 306, Shelby and Lafayette Streets, Detroit, Michigan, 1906-1907
      - Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate
        - Architectural Drawings, ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 23-1/4x34 to 26x37 inches
          - East, North and Court Elevations (6), revised 2/18/1907 (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
          - Details for Lower Stories, South Elevation (7), revised 2/22/1907 (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
          - Detail for Top Stories, East Half of South Elevation, for Stairs in Rear Area and for Metal Window Frames in Light Court (8), revised 12/11/1906 (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
          - Detail for Top and Lower Stories of Typical Bays (9), revised 12/11/1906 (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
          - Detail for Top and Bottom Stories of End Bay, North Elevation (10), revised 12/11/1906 (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
          - Detail of Marble Work and Plaster Cornice in Hall and Vestibule (11-1/2), undated (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
          - Section A-B, Looking North, and Section thro' Stair, Looking East (12), revised 12/11/1906 (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
          - Portion of East Elevation of Basement, First and Second-Floor Corridors (13), revised 12/11/1906 (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
          - Section thro' Stairs between Fourth and Sixth Floors, Looking East, and Miscellaneous Details (14), revised 12/11/1906 (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
          - Interior Finish in Owen Building above Second Story (49), undated (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
          - Mezzanine, Second and Third Floor Plans (X), undated (Map-case 18, Folder 12)
    - Day Krolik Residence, Job No. 331, Detroit, Michigan, 1906-1907
      - Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate
        - Architectural Drawings, undated, except as noted, ink-on-linen drawings, 17x22-1/2 inches
          - Basement Plan (1), 2 drawings (Map-case 23, Folder 2)
          - Transverse Section (5), revised 2/4/1907 (Map-case 23, Folder 2)
          - West Elevation (7), revised 2/4/1907 (Map-case 23, Folder 2)
          - East Elevation (9) (Map-case 23, Folder 2)
          - Finish Details in Main Hall, Living Room and Dining Room (10) (Map-case 23, Folder 2)
          - Interior Details (11) (Map-case 23, Folder 2)
    - George G. Booth Residence at Cranbrook, Jobs No. 333 & 333-A, B, D-K, Birmingham, Michigan, 1907-1908 and 1913-1923
      - George G. Booth Residence by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 333)
        - Survey Document by Mason L. Brown & Co., Civil Engineers, Detroit, undated; Red, yellow and black ink drawing on linen, 31x37-1/2 inches
          - Contour Map of Proposed Residence Site for G. G. Booth, Esq., at Cranbrook (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, undated; Ink-on-linen drawings, 23x46
          - Basement Plan (1), 4/1/1907; revised 6/28/1907 (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Basement Piping Plan (1A), revised 7/23/1907 (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - First Floor Plan (2), revised 1/6/1908 (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Second Floor Plan (3), revised 4/11/1908 (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Third Floor and Roof Plan (4), revised 1/28/1908 (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Sections on Lines A-B and C-D (5), revised 6/5/1907 (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - South Elevation (6), revised 1/6/1908 (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - North Elevation (7) (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - East and West Elevations and Section thro' Rear Stairs (8), revised 6/5/1907 (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Plan of Retaining Walls and Out-Buildings (9), revised 3/2/1908; 30x33-1/2 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Elevations and Sections of Garage and Out-Buildings (10), revised 10/8/1907; 26x33-1/2 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Details of Wardrobes, Linen Closet, Laundry Cupboard, Butler's and Kitchen Pantries, and Window and Door Trim, etc. (11), 22-3/4x27-1/2 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Plans of Revised Portion of Second and Third Floors and Roof (15), revised 6/7/1907; 22-1/2x33 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Front Elevation and Window Elevations Showing Stonework (19), 6/11/1907; revised 6/20/1907; 18-1/2x27-1/2 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Layout of Terrace (134), 26x26 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
          - Plan and Details of Junk Garden and Terrace (135), 21-1/2x14 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 10)
      - Cottage for Gardener for George Booth Residence by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 333-A)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, undated; Ink-on-linen drawings, 12x25-1/4 inches
          - Foundation and First Floor Plans (1), 3/28/1908 (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - Attic and Roof Plan and Section (2) (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - South and East Elevations (3) (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - North and West Elevations (4) (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
      - Water Tower for George Booth Residence by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 333-B)
        - Architectural Construction Drawing, 8/3/1908; Ink-on-linen drawing, 33-1/2x22-1/2 inches
          - Plans and Details of Water Tower (1) (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
      - Addition to Water Tower for George Booth Residence by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 333-D)
        - Architectural Construction Drawing, 7/17/1913; Ink-on-linen drawing, 24-1/4x23 inches
          - Plans and Elevations (1) (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
      - Addition to Residence for George Booth by Albert Kahn, Architect (Job No. 333-E)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, 2/25/1918; Ink-on-linen drawings with blue pencil revisions, 25-3/4x42-1/4 to 24-3/4x46 inches
          - Basement Plan (1), revised 7/11/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - First Floor Plan (2), revised 8/27/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - Roof Plan (3), revised 3/4/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - East Elevation (4), revised 6/20/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - West and South Elevations (5), revised 4/2/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - Sections (6), revised 4/2/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - Details of Library (7), revised 3/4/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - Details of Sun Room, Office and Work Room, and Hall and Work Room (8), revised 4/2/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - Detail of Tile Radiator Enclosure in Sun Room (27), 10/15/1918; 18-1/4x18-1/2 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
        - Mechanical Construction Drawings, Ink-on-linen drawings
          - Basement Plan (1M), 2/26/1918; revised 7/11/1918; 25-3/4x45-1/2 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
          - Sun Room Plan and Sections--Heating System (2M), 12/31/1918; 17x30 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 11)
      - Addition to Residence for George Booth by Albert Kahn, Architect (Job No. 333-F)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, 6/19/1918; Ink-on-linen drawings with blue pencil revisions, 18-1/4x301/4inches
          - Basement Plan (1), revised 7/11/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - First Floor Plan (2), revised 8/8/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Second Floor Plan (3), revised 7/11/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Third Floor Plan (4), revised 6/29/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - West and North Elevations (5), revised 8/8/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - South Elevation and Section thro' Porch on Line A-A (6), revised 8/8/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - East Elevation of Dormer for Alcove, Section thro' Porch on Line B-B and Detail of Overhang at Bay (7), revised 8/8/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Details of Hall #37 and Main Stairs to Third Floor (8), undated (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Interior Details of Chamber #30 (9), undated, revised 9/14/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Interior Details of Dressing Rooms #32 & 35 (10), undated, revised 2/28/1919 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Interior Details of Chamber #33 (11), undated, revised 9/14/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Details of Chamber #33 (12), undated (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Details of Chamber #33 (12R), 9/13/1918; revised 9/26/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Details of Baths #31 & 36 (13R), undated, revised 9/13/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Interior Details of Porch (14), undated (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Interior Details of Hall #37 (15), undated (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - South and East Elevations (16), 9/11/1918; revised 11/21/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
          - Details of Fountain Basin (17), rev., 10/24/1918; 11/30/1918 (Map-case 1, Folder 12)
      - Additions to Residence for George Booth by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 333-G)
        - Architectural Construction Drawing, August 1918; Ink-on-linen drawing, 26-1/4x45-3/4 inches
          - Basement Plan and Terrace Wall Details (1), revised 1/10/1919 (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
      - Alterations and Additions to Service Wing of Residence for George Booth by Albert Kahn, Architect and Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 333-H)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, undated, revised 1/4/1922; Ink-on-linen drawings, 28-1/2x35 inches
          - Basement Plan (1) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
            (not revised)
          - First Floor Plan (2) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
          - Second Floor Plan (3) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
          - Third Floor and Roof Plan and Section thro' Common Room Wing (4) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
          - South Elevation (5) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
          - West and South Elevations of Common Room Wing (6) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
          - East Elevation (7) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
          - North Elevation (8) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
          - Interior Elevations and Sections (9) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
          - Interior Elevations (10) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
          - Common Room Details (125), 9/5/1919 (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
        - Mechanical Construction Drawing, 4/28/1919; Ink-on-linen drawing, 27-3/4x34-1/2 inches
          - Basement Plan (2M) (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
      - Additions to Residence for George Booth by Albert Kahn, Architect (Job No. 333-I)
        - Mechanical Construction Drawings, 12/12/1922; Ink-on-linen drawings, 30x49 inches
          - Basement Plan (1M) (Map-case 1, Folder 14)
          - First Floor Plan (2) (Map-case 1, Folder 14)
          - Second Floor Plan (3) (Map-case 1, Folder 14)
          - Third Floor Plan (4) (Map-case 1, Folder 14)
      - Alterations to Residence for George Booth by Albert Kahn, Architect (Job No. 333-J)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, Pencil-on-vellum drawings
          - Detail of Bookcases (1), 11/7/1923; 21-3/4x18-1/2 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
          - Detail of Balustrade for North Terrace (2), 11/15/1923; 26-3/4x21 inches (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
      - Alterations to Bath Rooms for Residence of George Booth by Albert Kahn, Architect (Job No. 333-K)
        - Architectural Construction Drawing, 12/6/1923; Pencil and red pencil drawing on vellum, 23-1/2x33-3/4 inches
          - Plans and Elevations of Guest Room Bath and Bath Rooms #37 & 41 (1), revised 1/9/1924 (Map-case 1, Folder 13)
    - Chalmers--Detroit Motor Company (E. R. Thomas--Detroit Company) Factory, Job No. 344 and 344-A and C, Detroit, Michigan, 1907-1909
      - E. R. Thomas--Detroit Company Factory Building Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 344)
        - Architectural Drawings, 5/10/1907; ink-on-linen drawings, 19-1/2x57 inches
          - Foundation Plan (1) (Tube 56)
          - First Floor Plan (2), revised 6/7/1907 (Tube 56)
          - [Second Floor Plan] (Tube 56)
          - Roof Plan (4) (Tube 56)
          - East and West Elevations (5) (Tube 56)
          - North and South Elevations, Sections, and Details of Main Entrance, Stairs and Sliding Tin Doors (6), revised 6/7/1907 (Tube 56)
          - Exterior Elevation, Sections of Wall and Column, and Details of Outside Elevator Doors and Outside Doors (7), revised 6/5/1907 (Tube 56)
          - Typical, Full-Sized Details of Door and Window Frames (8) (Tube 56)
          - Plan of Office and Elevations of Corridors and Partitions (14), revised 8/10/1907 (Tube 56)
      - E. R. Thomas-Detroit Company Power Building Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 344-A)
        - Architectural Drawings, 5/20/1907; ink-on-linen drawings, 29x28 inches
          - Plans of Foundation, First Floor and Roof (1), revised 6/24/1907 (Map-case 24, Folder 8)
          - North, South, East and West Elevations (2), revised 6/21/1907 (Map-case 24, Folder 8)
          - Exterior Elevation, Half-Section, and Details of Outside Doors, Coal Doors and Partitions (3), revised 6/8/1907 (Map-case 24, Folder 8)
          - Typical, Full-Sized Details of Window and Door Frames (4) (Map-case 24, Folder 8)
      - Chalmers-Detroit Motor Company Factory Building Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 344-C)
        - Architectural and Mechanical Drawings, 4/14/1909; ink-on-vellum drawings with pencil notations, 19x56 inches, except as noted
          - Plot Plan (1-A), undated; 19-1/2x28 inches (Tube 56)
          - Plot Plan (1-B), 5/24/1907; 22x28 inches (Tube 56)
          - First Floor Plan (2), revised 12/16/1909 (Tube 56)
          - Second Floor Plan (3) (Tube 56)
          - Third Floor Plan (4), revised 7/6/1909 (Tube 56)
          - Full-Sized Detail of Box Frames (9) (Tube 56)
          - First Floor Plan of Steam Heating (1-M), undated (Tube 56)
          - Map of Underground of The Chalmers Motor Company, Detroit, undated; 5 prints (black-and-white; 7-1/2x9-1/2-inch), 2 drawings (one ink-on-linen and one blueprint-on-linen; 28x71 inches and 29-1/2x72-1/2 inches, respectively) (Tube 56)
    - Mergenthaler Linotype Company Office Building, Job No. 349, Brooklyn, New York, 1907
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, 27 drawings (Map-case 33, Folder 1)
    - Mergenthaler Linotype Company Addition, Job No. 349-A, Brooklyn, New York, 1912
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural and Plumbing, 10 drawings (Map-case 33, Folder 2)
    - Standard Auto Company Garage and Showroom, Job No. 355, Woodward and Garfield Avenues, Detroit, Michigan, 1907-1908
      - Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate
        - Architectural Drawings, ink-on-linen drawings, 28x35 inches (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
          - Foundation Plan (1), 9/28/1907 (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
          - First Floor Plan (2), revised 3/2/1908 (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
          - Plan of Heating and Lighting and Riser Diagrams (2-A), revised 3/2/1908 (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
          - Roof Plan (3), revised 2/13/1908 (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
          - Woodward and Garfield Avenues Elevations and South and East Elevations (4), revised 3/2/1908 (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
          - Transverse and Longitudinal Sections and Miscellaneous Sections and Details (5), revised 2/13/1908 (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
          - Detail of Woodward Avenue Front (6), revised 10/25/1907 (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
          - Part Elevations of Woodward Avenue Front and Section, Showing Anchors for Tops of Piers (7) (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
          - Elevations of East and West Portions on Garfield Avenue (8) (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
          - Interior Elevations of Showroom and Offices (9), revised 3/2/1908 (Map-case 24, Folder 10)
    - William L. Clements Residence, Job No. 362 and 362-D, Bay City, Michigan, 1908-1909 and 1924
      - Design Development Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 362)
        - Architectural Drawings, undated; Ink-on-linen drawings
          - First Floor Plan, 14-1/4x24-3/4 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Second Floor Plan, 14x24-1/4 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - First Floor Plan, 25-1/2x43 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Second Floor Plan, 26-1/4x43-1/2 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
      - Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 362)
        - Architectural Drawings, March 1908; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 24-3/4x43-1/2 to 26-1/2x43-1/2 inches
          - Plot Plan (1-A), revised 7/3/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Basement Plan (1), revised 7/17/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - First Floor Plan (2), revised 7/17/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Second Floor Plan (3), revised 7/17/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Third Floor and Roof Plan and Details of Pantry Fittings (4), revised 7/17/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Sections (5), revised 5/18/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - South Elevation (6) (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - East and West Elevations (7), revised 5/18/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - North Elevation (8), revised 5/18/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Interior Details (9) (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Details of Living Room, Dining Room, Drawing Room, Den and Chambers (10), revised 5/18/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Elevations of Music Room and Breakfast Room (11), revised 5/18/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - North Elevation of Music Room and Details of Bathrooms and Finish on Second Floor (12), revised 5/18/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Window Details (13) (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Plans, Elevations and Sections of Stable (14), revised 7/3/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Details of Alterations to Music Swell Box and Revised Third Floor Plan and Portion of Elevations (15), revised 9/3/1908 (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Plan and Section of Dining Room Bay (24), 18-1/2x12 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
          - Details for Pergola (95), 6/18/1909; 15x25 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
      - Construction Drawing by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects (Job No. 362-D)
        - Architectural Drawing, 8/1/1924; Pencil-on-linen drawing, 21-1/4x25-1/4 inches
          - Details of Changes in Basement Library (1) (Map-case 18, Folder 1)
    - Henry B. Joy Residence ("Fairacres"), Job No. 368 and 368-A, F, G, J, L, M & N, Grosse Pointe, Michigan, 1908-1909; 1914-1915; 1926; 1928
      - Henry B. Joy Residence Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No 368)
        - Architectural Design Development Drawings, undated; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil sketching and notations
          - Site Plan, 17-3/4x30-1/4 inches (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
          - Basement Plan, 24x44-3/4 inches (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, 8/22/1908; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 24-1/2x45 inches
          - Basement Plan (1), revised 7/2/1909 (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
          - First Floor Plan (2), revised 1/8/1909 (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
          - Second Floor Plan (3), revised 1/8/1909 (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
          - Third Floor Plan (4), revised 1/8/1909 (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
          - Section on Line "A-B," Section thro' Main Cornice and Details of Mantels and Windows (5), undated (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
          - East and West Elevations (6), undated (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
          - Main Hall Details (9), revised 1/8/1909 (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
          - Details of Terrace Walls and Walks at East Front of House (14), 7/18/1908; 11x29-1/2 inches (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
          - Gate and Fence Details (94), revised 12/7/1909; 15x23 inches (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
          - Details of Fences on East, North and West Property Lines, Entrances and Barnyard, 30-3/4x48-1/2 inches (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
            (not numbered or dated due to linen damage)
        - Mechanical Construction Drawing, undated; Ink-on-linen drawing with pencil sketching, 31-1/2x62-1/2 inches
          - Plot Plan Showing Sewer, Water amd Drain Pipes (Map-case 16, Folder 4)
            (not numbered due to linen damage)
      - Henry B. Joy Residence Garage Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 368-A)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 18-1/4x28-1/2 inches
          - Plans of Foundation and First and Second Floors (1), revised 6/19/1909 (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Plans of First and Second Floors (1), 7/9/1908; 14-1/4x27 inches (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Elevations and Sections (2), 3/16/1909 (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Corner of East Elevation Showing Detail of Brick Work and Detail of Truss "A" (3), 3/16/1909 (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Corner of West Elevation, Detail of Truss "B" and Section thru' Truss (4), undated (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Design for Alternating Figure-Elevations and Cross-Section (5), 3/16/1909 (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Details of Truss Reinforcement (13), undated; 19-1/4x34-1/4 inches (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
      - Henry B. Joy Residence Boat House by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 368 and 368-F)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings of Boat House (Job 368), undated; Blueprints, 18x22 to 20x27-1/4 inches
          - Site Plan (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Foundation Plan, 2 prints (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings of Addition to Boat House (Job No. 368-F), Ink and pencil drawings on tracing paper with notations, 16x27-1/2 to 15-1/4x32 inches
          - Foundation Plan and Section thru' Dock (1), 11/3/1914 (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Floor Plan (2), undated (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Roof Plan (3), undated (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - North and South Elevation (4), undated (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - East Elevation (5), undated (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Transverse Section and Section of Cornice (6), 12/1/1914 (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Section thru' Saddle between Old and New Boat House (7), undated (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - Roof Framing Plan and Details of Framing (8), 11/4/1914 (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
      - New Concrete Boat Dock (Job No. 368-G)
        - Architectural Construction Drawing, 2/24/1915; revised 3/1/1915; Ink-on-linen drawing, 18-1/2x22-1/4 inches
          - Plan of New Concrete Dock and Section thro' Beam Where New Concrete Dock Adjoins Present Boat House (1) (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
        - Structural Construction Drawing, 1/2/1915; revised 3/1/1915; Ink-on-linen drawing, 19x29-1/2 inches
          - Section "AA" and Details of Beams "A" and "B" (1-S) (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
      - Alterations to Garage by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects (Job No. 368-J)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, 3/17/1926; Pencil drawings on tracing paper, 16x28-1/2 inches
          - Plans of First and Second Floors and Roof (1) (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
          - North and West Elevations, Details of Balcony and Stair and Wardrobe in Chamber #1, and Section thru' Truss "B" and Rear Wall (2) (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
        - Structural Construction Drawing, 3/9/1926; Pencil drawing on tracing paper, 16-1/4x29 inches
          - Alteration and Reinforcement of Truss "B" (1-S) (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
        - Mechanical Construction Drawing, 3/26/1926; Ink-on-linen drawing, 16-1/4x29-1/4 inches
          - Plans of First and Second Floors (1-M) (Map-case 16, Folder 5)
      - Office Addition to Residence by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects (Job No. 368-L)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, undated